Finding aid for Marvin Lemmon Niehuss Papers, 1923-1972 (bulk 1941-1968)
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical Files, 1923-1972
  - 1957-1958
    - Atmospheric Research (Box 7)
    - A.U.R.A. (Box 7)
    - B (Box 7)
    - C (Box 7)
    - Computer Committee (Box 7)
    - D (Box 7)
    - Development Council (Box 7)
    - E (Box 7)
    - Engineering College (Box 7)
    - Engineering Research Institute (Box 7)
    - Engineering Research Institute--Reorganization of (Box 7)
    - Faculty Periodic Medical Examinations (Box 7)
    - Gerontology (Box 7)
    - Governing Boards, Association of (Box 7)
    - Grant Requests (Box 7)
    - H (Box 7)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 7)
    - Institute for Defense Analysis (Box 7)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (Box 7)
    - Lectures, University (Box 7)
    - Literary College (Box 7)
    - Medical School (Box 7)
    - Nurses Training Program--Northwestern College (Box 7)
    - Outside Offers to Our Faculty Members (Box 7)
    - Outside and Part-time Employment (Box 7)
    - Part-time (Outside Employment) (Box 7)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 7)
    - Professorship--Alice Freeman Palmer (Box 7)
    - Project Michigan (Box 7)
    - Regents (Box 7)
    - Russell Report (Box 7)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 7)
    - Senate, University (Box 7)
    - Space Research (Box 7)
    - Student-Faculty-Administration Steering Committee (Box 7)
    - University Hospital (Box 7)
    - University Hospital--Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 7)
    - Vision Research, Committee of Management (Box 7)
    - Visitors (Box 7)
    - Wayne State University (Box 7)
  - 1958-1959
    - A (Box 8)
    - Admissions (Box 8)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 8)
    - Architecture and Design (Box 8)
    - Architecture and Design--Landscape Architecture (Box 8)
    - Atmospheric Research, University Committee on (Box 8)
    - Automobile Safety Research Committee (Box 8)
    - B (Box 8)
    - Center for Research on Conflict Resolution (Box 8)
    - Center for Study of Higher Education (Box 8)
    - Chrysler Institute of Technology (Box 8)
    - Citizens' Research Council (Box 8)
    - Deans' Conference Education, School of (Box 8)
    - Employee Benefits (Box 8)
    - Engineering College (Box 8)
    - Engineering Research Institute--Compensation (Box 8)
    - Faculty Periodic Medical Examinations (Box 8)
    - Flint College (Box 8)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 8)
    - G (Box 8)
    - Gifts (Box 8)
    - Governor's Science Advisory Board (Box 8)
    - Grant Requests (Box 8)
    - H (Box 8)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 8)
    - Hatcher, Harlan--Letters Answered for (Box 8)
    - Honors Convocation (Box 8)
    - Hospital administration (Box 8)
    - Hyma, Albert (Box 8)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 8)
    - International Cooperation Administration (Box 8)
    - Junior Year Abroad (Box 8)
    - L (Box 8)
    - Lectures, University (Box 8)
    - M (Box 8)
    - Medical School (Box 8)
    - Mexico, Comite Norteamericano Pro (Box 8)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 8)
    - Outside Offers to Faculty Members (Box 8)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 8)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 8)
    - Press, University of Michigan (Box 8)
    - Project Michigan (Box 8)
    - Research Institute (Box 8)
    - R.O.T.C. (Box 8)
    - Russell Study (Box 8)
    - Science and Technology, Institute (Box 8)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 8)
    - Senate, University (Box 8)
    - Severance Pay (Box 8)
    - Sigma Kappa Case (Box 8)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 8)
    - Tehuantepec, Mexico--Tropical Center (Box 8)
    - Travel Grants, Inter-University Committee on (Box 8)
    - Visitors (Box 8)
    - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 8)
    - Williams, R.L. (Box 8)
    - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 8)
  - 1959-1960
    - A-L [Missing] (Box 9)
    - M (Box 9)
    - Marcus, Benjamin (Box 9)
    - Medical Education, Committee on (Box 9)
    - Medical School (Box 9)
    - Medical Science Building (Box 9)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 9)
    - Michigan Research Council (Box 9)
    - N (Box 9)
    - National Conference on Rural Health (Box 9)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 9)
    - Outside Offers to Faculty Members (Box 9)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 9)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 9)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 9)
    - R (Box 9)
    - Regents (Box 9)
    - Research Institute (Box 9)
    - S (Box 9)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 9)
    - Senate, University (Box 9)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 9)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 9)
    - Special Science Advisory Committee (Box 9)
    - Suomalainen Dinner (Box 9)
    - T (Box 9)
    - University Hospital
      - General (Box 9)
      - Minutes and Agenda (Box 9)
      - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 9)
    - Visitors (Box 9)
    - W (Box 9)
    - Wayne State University (Box 9)
    - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 9)
    - Williams, R.L. (Box 9)
    - XYZ (Box 9)
  - 1960-1961
    - A (Box 9)
    - Accreditation Reports (Box 9)
    - Admissions (Box 9)
    - Alumni Association (Box 9)
    - Architecture Department (Box 9)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 9)
    - Architecture and Design, College of--Landscape Architecture (Box 9)
    - Asian Studies, Association for (Box 9)
    - B (Box 9)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 9)
    - C (Box 9)
    - Calendar Studies (Year-Round) (Box 9)
    - Candidates for Positions (Box 9)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Box 9)
    - Center for Study of Higher Education (Box 9)
    - Citizens for Michigan (Box 9)
    - Cohen, Wilbur (Box 9)
    - Conductron Corporation (Box 9)
    - Dearborn Center (Box 9)
    - Dental School (Box 9)
    - Dorr, Harold M. (Box 9)
    - Education, School of (Box 9)
    - Engineering College (Box 9)
    - F (Box 9)
    - Flint College (Box 9)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 9)
    - General Motors (Box 9)
    - Generalist--University of Chicago (Box 9)
    - Gifts (Box 9)
    - Governor's Office (Box 9)
    - Graduate School (Box 9)
    - Grand Valley College Board (Box 9)
    - Grant Requests (Box 9)
    - H (Box 10)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 10)
    - Hospital administration (Box 10)
    - I (Box 10)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Intercultural Relations, Committee on (Box 10)
    - International Cooperation Administration (Box 10)
    - J (Box 10)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute (Box 10)
    - L (Box 10)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (Box 10)
    - Lee, Gilbert (Box 10)
    - Legislators (Box 10)
    - Library (Box 10)
    - Literary College (Box 10)
    - Mc (Box 10)
    - M (Box 10)
    - Marcus, Benjam (Greater Muskegon) (Box 10)
    - Medical School (Box 10)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 10)
    - Michigan Association of the Professions (Box 10)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 10)
    - Michigan State University (Box 10)
    - Music, School of (Box 10)
    - N (Box 10)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 10)
    - National Training Laboratories, Committee on (Box 10)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 10)
    - Nelson, Lyle M. (Box 10)
    - O (Box 10)
    - Oral Surgery (Box 10)
    - Outside Offers to Faculty Members (Box 10)
    - Overhead Charges for Research (Box 10)
    - P (Box 10)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 10)
    - Pierpont, W.K. (Box 10)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 10)
    - Primate Research Center (Box 10)
    - Professorship--Alice Freeman Palmer (Box 10)
    - Professorships--Distinguished (Box 10)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 10)
    - Q (Box 10)
    - R (Box 10)
    - Recommendations (Box 10)
    - Regents (Box 10)
    - Research Institute (Box 10)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Box 10)
    - S (Box 10)
    - Science and Technology Institute of (Box 10)
    - Section 15--Public Law 1102 (Box 10)
    - Senate (Box 10)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 10)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 10)
    - Staff Benefits, Office of (Box 10)
    - T (Box 10)
    - Theatre Group (Box 10)
    - Travel Grants (Box 10)
    - Tropical Studies, Proposed Center for (Box 10)
    - University Hospital (Box 10)
    - University Hospital--Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 10)
    - Visitors (Box 10)
    - Wayne State University (Box 10)
    - Wayne County General Hospital (Box 10)
    - XYZ (Box 10)
  - 1961-1962
    - A (Box 11)
    - Admissions (Box 11)
    - Alumni Association (Box 11)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 11)
    - Architecture, Department of (Box 11)
    - Architecture and Design, College of
      - General (Box 11)
      - Landscape Architecture (Box 11)
      - Urban Planning Committee (Box 11)
    - Area and International Studies Committee (Box 11)
    - Asian Studies, Center for Southern (Box 11)
    - Association of Governing Boards (Box 11)
    - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy (Box 11)
    - Atmospheric Research, University Committee on (Box 11)
    - B (Box 11)
    - Brinser, Ayers (Box 11)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 11)
    - C (Box 11)
    - Calendar Studies (Year-Round) (Box 11)
    - Center for the Study of Higher Education (Box 11)
    - Chambers, M.M. (Box 11)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J. (Box 11)
    - College Relations, Committee on (Box 11)
    - Con-Con (Box 11)
    - D (Box 11)
    - Data Processing Center (Box 11)
    - Dearborn Center (Box 11)
    - Development Council (Box 11)
    - Discrimination (Box 11)
    - Dorr, H.M. (Box 11)
    - E (Box 11)
    - Education, School of (Box 11)
    - Engineering College (Box 11)
    - F (Box 11)
    - Faculty Achievement Awards Committee (Box 11)
    - Faculty Periodic Medical Exams (Box 11)
    - Faculty Privileges (Box 11)
    - Fees, Committee (Box 11)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 11)
    - G (Box 11)
    - General Fund (Box 11)
    - General Motors (Box 11)
    - Grant Requests (Box 11)
    - H (Box 11)
    - Hatcher, Harlan H. (Box 11)
    - Heart Center (Box 11)
    - Hospital Administration, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - H.R. 6984 (Box 11)
    - Indian Studies, American Institute of (Box 11)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 11)
    - J (Box 11)
    - Junior Year Abroad, Committee on (Box 11)
    - K (Box 11)
    - L (Box 11)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of (Box 11)
    - Latin American Language and Area Study (Box 11)
    - Law School (Box 11)
    - Lectures (Box 11)
    - Lee, Gilbert (Box 11)
    - Legislative Audit Commission (Box 11)
    - Lewis, Vice President (Box 11)
    - Library (Box 11)
    - Literary College (Box 11)
    - Loyalty Oath (Box 11)
    - M (Box 11)
    - Master's Degree Program--3 Year (Box 11)
    - Medical School (Box 11)
    - Metal Casting (Box 11)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Public Higher Education (Box 11)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 11)
    - Michigan State University (Box 11)
    - Military Retirement System, Study of (Box 11)
    - Mott Foundation (Box 11)
    - Music, School of (Box 11)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 12)
    - National Training Laboratories (Box 12)
    - Outside Offers to Faculty Members (Box 12)
    - Overhead Negotiation (Box 12)
    - P (Box 12)
    - Peace Corps (Box 12)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 12)
    - Pierpont, W.K. (Box 12)
    - Polar Research, University Committee on (Box 12)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 12)
    - Press, University of Michigan (Box 12)
    - Programmed Learning, Committee on (Box 12)
    - Public Administration, Institute of (Box 12)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 12)
    - R (Box 12)
    - Reed Report (Box 12)
    - Registration and Records, Office of (Box 12)
    - Regents (Box 12)
    - Russell Report (Box 12)
    - Russian Exchange (Box 12)
    - S (Box 12)
    - Science and Technology, Institute for (Box 12)
    - Security (Box 12)
    - Senate, University (Box 12)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 12)
    - Senate Concurrent Resolution No. 40 (Box 12)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 12)
    - Space Age Research Conference (Box 12)
    - Speaker Policy (Box 12)
    - Sponsored Research (Box 12)
    - T (Box 12)
    - Travel Grants (Box 12)
    - Tropical Studies, Proposed Center for (Box 12)
    - TV--Professor Garrison (Box 12)
    - Veterans Readjustment Center (Box 12)
    - Vetulonia, Italy Excavations (Box 12)
    - Visitors (Box 12)
    - W (Box 12)
    - Water Pollution Control Laboratory (Box 12)
    - Wayne State University (Box 12)
  - 1962-1963
    - A (Box 12)
    - Achievement Awards, Outstanding (Box 12)
    - Admissions (Box 12)
    - Alumni Association (Box 12)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 12)
    - American Council on Education (Box 12)
    - Architecture, Department of (Box 12)
    - Army Audit Agency (Box 12)
    - Athletic Board (Box 12)
    - B (Box 12)
    - Blue Cross (Box 12)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 12)
    - C (Box 12)
    - Chambers, M.M. (Box 12)
    - Chrysler Corporation (Box 12)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J. (Box 12)
    - Conductron (Box 12)
    - Congressional Record Digest (Box 12)
    - Cost Computation, Indirect (Box 12)
    - Cross, Robert N. (Box 12)
    - D (Box 12)
    - Delta College (Box 12)
    - Delta College (Box 13)
    - Education, School of (Box 13)
    - Elzay, Jack (Box 13)
    - Engineering College (Box 13)
    - English Language Institute (Box 13)
    - Faculty Center (Box 13)
    - Faculty Salaries (Box 13)
    - Federal (Box 13)
    - Flint College (Box 13)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 13)
    - G (Box 13)
    - General Motors (Box 13)
    - Generalist
      - University of Minnesota (Box 13)
      - National League for Nursing (Box 13)
    - Gifts (Box 13)
    - Grand Valley State College (Box 13)
    - Grant Requests (Box 13)
    - Grass Roots (Box 13)
    - H (Box 13)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 13)
    - Heyns, Roger (Box 13)
    - Hospital Administration (Box 13)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 13)
    - J (Box 13)
    - Jackson County Community College (Box 13)
    - Junior Year Abroad (Box 13)
    - K (Box 13)
    - L (Box 13)
    - Lectures, University (Box 13)
    - Legislative Audit Commission (Box 13)
    - Literary College (Box 13)
    - M (Box 13)
    - Medical School (Box 13)
    - Medical Science and Research Building (Box 13)
    - Michigan Association of the Professions (Box 13)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Public Higher Education (Box 13)
    - N (Box 13)
    - Non-Resident Students (Box 13)
    - Oxford Housing Project (Box 13)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 13)
    - Pierpont, W.K. (Box 13)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 13)
    - Project Michigan (Box 13)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 13)
    - Regents (Box 13)
    - Research Park (Box 13)
    - Romney, George (Box 13)
    - Russian Exchange (Box 13)
    - S (Box 13)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 13)
    - Security (Box 13)
    - Senate, University (Box 13)
    - Senate Committee on Improvement of Instruction (Box 13)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 13)
    - Staff Excellence, Committee on (Box 13)
    - Swainson, John B. (Box 13)
    - T (Box 13)
    - Theatre Project (Box 14)
    - Travel Grants (Box 14)
    - University Hospital
      - General (Box 14)
      - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 14)
      - Veteran Readjustment Center (Box 14)
    - Vetulonia, Italy--Excavations (Box 14)
    - Vice President for Research (Box 14)
    - Visiting Committees (Box 14)
    - Visitors (Box 14)
    - W (Box 14)
    - Williams, R.L. (Box 14)
  - 1963-1964
    - A (Box 14)
    - Administration, Department of--Lansing (Box 14)
    - Admissions (Box 14)
    - Alumni Association (Box 14)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 14)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 14)
    - Army Audit Agency (Box 14)
    - Athletic Board (Box 14)
    - B (Box 14)
    - Blue Ribbon Committee on Higher Education, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - C (Box 14)
    - Chrysler Corporation (Box 14)
    - Con-Con (Box 14)
    - Cost Reduction (Box 14)
    - D (Box 14)
    - Delta College (Box 14)
    - Development Council (Box 14)
    - Education and World Affairs Meeting at MSU (Box 14)
    - Electromagnetic Research, Center for (Box 14)
    - Enrollment--Non-Resident Students (Box 14)
    - F (Box 14)
    - Federal Government (Box 14)
    - Flint College (Box 14)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 14)
    - General Motors (Box 14)
    - Gifts (Box 14)
    - Grant Requests (Box 14)
    - H (Box 14)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 14)
    - Heyns, Roger (Box 14)
    - Honorary Degrees, Committee on (Box 14)
    - Hospital Administration (Box 14)
    - Housing (Box 14)
    - I (Box 14)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 14)
    - K (Box 14)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 14)
    - Lee, Gilbert (Box 14)
    - Legislative Audit Commission (Box 14)
    - Legislators (Box 14)
    - Levinson, Ben (Box 14)
    - Library--Central Campus (Box 14)
    - Mc (Box 14)
    - M (Box 14)
    - Markle Foundation (Box 14)
    - Medical School (Box 15)
    - Medical School--Expansion of Medical Education (Box 15)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 15)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Public Higher Education (Box 15)
    - Michigan Department of Economic Expansion (Box 15)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 15)
    - Michigan Hospital Service (Box 15)
    - Michigan State University Medical School (Box 15)
    - N (Box 15)
    - Nelson, Lyle (Box 15)
    - O (Box 15)
    - Operation Michigan (Box 15)
    - P (Box 15)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 15)
    - Pierpont, W.K. (Box 15)
    - Plant Extension Committee (Box 15)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 15)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 15)
    - R (Box 15)
    - Regents (Box 15)
    - Residential College (Box 15)
    - Romney, George (Box 15)
    - S (Box 15)
    - Scholarships (Box 15)
    - Scholarships--Merit (Box 15)
    - Section 15 (Box 15)
    - Senate, University (Box 15)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 15)
    - Sesquicentennial
      - Campaign (Box 15)
      - Central Committee (Box 15)
      - Interviewer Letters (Box 15)
      - Minutes (Box 15)
      - Planning Committee (Box 15)
    - Television Instruction (Box 15)
    - Thurnan Will (Box 15)
    - Travel Grants (Box 15)
    - Union-League Merger (Box 15)
    - University Hospital (Box 15)
    - U-M '63 and U-M '64 Programs (Box 15)
    - U.S. Government (Box 15)
    - Visitors (Box 15)
    - W (Box 15)
  - 1964-1965
    - A (Box 15)
    - Act 245 (Box 15)
    - Admissions (Box 15)
    - Alumni Association (Box 15)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 15)
    - Army Audit Agency (Box 15)
    - Audio-Visual Center Report (Box 15)
    - B (Box 15)
    - Blue Ribbon Committee on Higher Education (Box 15)
    - Branch Colleges (Box 16)
    - Brazil--A.I.C. Contracts (Box 16)
    - Business Administration, Graduate School of (Box 16)
    - C (Box 16)
    - Calendar, Academic (Box 16)
    - California, University of (Box 16)
    - Chrysler Corporation (Box 16)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 16)
    - Community Colleges (Box 16)
    - Computer Facilities (Box 16)
    - Con-Con (Box 16)
    - Cross, Robert N. (Box 16)
    - Cutler, Richard (Box 16)
    - D (Box 16)
    - Davis Report (Box 16)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 16)
    - Dental School (Box 16)
    - Distinguished Faculty Achievement Awards Committee (Box 16)
    - Distinguished Professorships (Box 16)
    - Distinguished University Fellowship (Box 16)
    - E (Box 16)
    - Eaton, Berrien (Box 16)
    - Enrollment (Box 16)
    - F (Box 16)
    - Fees--Non-Resident (Box 16)
    - Flint College, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 16)
    - G (Box 16)
    - Gemini 4 (Box 16)
    - General Departmental Communications (Box 16)
    - General Motors (Box 16)
    - Gifts (Box 16)
    - Grant Requests (Box 16)
    - H (Box 16)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 16)
    - Higgins Student Aid Fund (Box 16)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of (Box 16)
    - Honorary Degrees, Committee on (Box 16)
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of (Box 16)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 16)
    - J (Box 16)
    - K (Box 16)
    - L (Box 16)
    - Law School (Box 16)
    - Lee, Gilbert (Box 16)
    - Literary College (Box 16)
    - Mc (Box 16)
    - M (Box 16)
    - Medical School (Box 16)
    - Medical Science Unit II (Box 16)
    - Michigan Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 17)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Higher Education (Box 17)
    - Michigan Health Council (Box 17)
    - Michigan Hospital Service, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - N (Box 17)
    - N.A.S.A. (Box 17)
    - Norville Family Fund (Box 17)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 17)
    - P (Box 17)
    - Parking--North Campus (Box 17)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 17)
    - Pierpont, W.K. (Box 17)
    - Plant Extension Committee (Box 17)
    - Presidents, Council of (Box 17)
    - R (Box 17)
    - Regents (Box 17)
    - Research, Vice President for (Box 17)
    - Residence Problems (Box 17)
    - Residential College (Box 17)
    - Role Committee (Box 17)
    - S (Box 17)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 17)
    - Senate, University (Box 17)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 17)
    - State Board of Education (Box 17)
    - Teach-in (Box 17)
    - Trigon (Box 17)
    - Tropical Studies, Organization for (Box 17)
    - Tuition File (Box 17)
    - University Hospital (Box 17)
    - University Hospital--Sate Agency Hospital Proposed (Box 17)
    - V (Box 17)
    - Vietnam (Box 17)
    - Visitors (Box 17)
    - W (Box 17)
    - Year Round Operation (Box 17)
  - 1965-1966
    - Administration, Department of--Lansing (Box 17)
    - Admissions (Box 17)
    - American Council on Education (Box 17)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 17)
    - Attorney General's Opinion (Box 17)
    - B (Box 17)
    - Bequests (Box 17)
    - Book Store--University (Box 17)
    - Budget--General Fund (Box 17)
    - Building Projects Proposed (Box 17)
    - Business Administration, Graduate School of (Box 17)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (Box 17)
    - Center for the Study of Higher Education (Box 17)
    - Consolidated Budget (Box 17)
    - Cutler, Richard (Box 17)
    - D (Box 18)
    - Eastern Michigan University (Box 18)
    - Education, Compact for (Box 18)
    - Engineering College (Box 18)
    - F (Box 18)
    - Faxon Committee (Box 18)
    - Flint College (Box 18)
    - G (Box 18)
    - General Motors (Box 18)
    - Gifts (Box 18)
    - H (Box 18)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 18)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 18)
    - Higgins, George N. (Box 18)
    - Hospital Administration, Bureau of (Box 18)
    - Hutchinson Act (Box 18)
    - I (Box 18)
    - Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 18)
    - K (Box 18)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 18)
    - Legislators (Box 18)
    - M (Box 18)
    - Medical School (Box 18)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 18)
    - Michigan Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 18)
    - Michigan Information Center (Box 18)
    - Michigan Hospital Service (Box 18)
    - Plant Extension Committee (Box 18)
    - Power, Eugene--Xerox (Box 18)
    - Presidents, Council of, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 18)
    - Radock, Michael (Box 18)
    - Recommendations (Box 18)
    - Regents (Box 18)
    - Residential College (Box 18)
    - Role Committee (Box 18)
    - S (Box 18)
    - Senate, University (Box 18)
    - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 18)
    - Smith, Allan (Box 18)
    - Social Research--Building Dedication (Box 18)
    - Space Utilization Study (Box 19)
    - State Board of Education (Box 19)
    - Transportation, American Academy of (Box 19)
    - University Hospital (Box 19)
    - Visitors (Box 19)
    - W (Box 19)
    - Willow Village (Box 19)
  - 1966-1967
    - A (Box 19)